Guide to the Collective: Unconscious Archive MSS.225
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Administrative Files
  - Subseries C: Financial
    - Receipts, checks, and other misc. financial records, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Phone bills (Bell Atlantic, Verizon), 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Receipts, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Receipts, ledger, and other misc. financial records, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Checking account statements and other financial reports, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Checks and check stubs, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Checks, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Operating reports and tax records, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Fire protection receipts/reports, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Checks and check stubs, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Electric bills (ConEd), 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Garbage and city waste invoices, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Receipts, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Petty cash receipts, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Misc. financial records, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Deposits, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Receipts, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Deposits, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Deposits, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Deposits, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Not-For-Profit/Tax exemption records, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Tax exemption records, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising/grant files, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Tax exempt info/forms (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Misc. receipts [IFAM?], undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Donations, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Series III: Photographic Material
  Series III: Photographic Material contains negatives, slides, and photographs pertaining to Collective members and activities. This series includes a large volume of snapshots, interspersed with what appear to be production shots and a few promotional images. Many of the photographs appear to be water-damaged and most lack documentation.
  - Slides - misc., 1994-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    photographer: Allan B. Spiegel
  - Photographs - misc. "Monster Parade", [ca. 1996-2000] (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - "Shrimpdiabloinmypants Film Festival", [1999] (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - Charlie Victor Romeo, [ca. 1999-2001] (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photographs - "Dinner Performance", 9/24/00, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Negatives and Photographs - "5th Annual Monster Parade", [2000] (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Negatives - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Photographs - misc., undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Photographs - head shots, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Photocopies [postcard size] (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Photocopies, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Series IV: Realia
  Series IV: Realia contains a variety of objects likely used as stage props as well as a small number of artworks.
  Box 8 will be stored with other oversize materials.
  - Tristan Perich, "One Bit Music" (Cantaloupe Music), 2004-2005 (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0001)
  - Artwork - Matthew Deleget, "Fortress", 2000 (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0002)
    Silver metallic ink on black handmade paper on masonite board
  - Artwork - C. Smith [untitled harbor scene], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0003)
    matted photocopy
  - Artwork [untitled nudes collage], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0004)
    pencil, paint, and pastel on canvas
  - Artwork - A.R. Ceheralu [sp?], "Nike Tsunami #17", 2005 (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0005)
    holographic tile
  - Artwork - [Hitler cutout], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0006)
    marker and crayon on wax paper
  - Sketchbook - Gecko, undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0007)
  - Artwork - Jake Young [?], "Happy 10th Faceboy!", undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0008)
  - Woven fabric portrait [Karl Marx], undated (Box 8, Object ID: 225.2.0009)
  - "Borscht Belt" decorated wrestling belt, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0010)
  - Promotional coffee cups [4], C:U and Coffee Cup Productions, 2001 (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0011)
  - "Arsenal" perfume cannister [in shape of grenade], undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0012)
  - Metal bike horn, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0013)
  - Toy gun, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0014)
  - Toy gun, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0015)
  - Toy gun, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0016)
  - Disposable camera, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0017)
  - Antique telephone, 1945 (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0018)
  - Toy knife, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0019)
  - Doorbell, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0020)
  - Clear plastic tubing, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0021)
  - Mirror ball christmas ornaments, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0022)
  - Furry red glove, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0023)
  - Transparent red scarf, undated (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0024)
  - Event lanyards - "Auto-Historical Anniversary Event 5", 4/8/2000 (Box 9, Object ID: 225.2.0025)
- Series V: Video
  Series V: Video includes original footage of Collective: Unconscious productions, commercial videos, as well as source material collected as background research for productions and as documentation of other avant-garde artists. Subseries B, Originals includes recordings on various media of Collective: Unconscious performances. The bulk of material documents the anti-slams, episodes of Manifestations, and Faceboy. Series C, Miscellaneous, contains recordings collected by Collective: Unconscious, including commercial films, independent productions by contemporary and avant-garde artists, mixed recordings of source materials (primarily archival footage and television productions), and unidentified tapes.
  Subseries A: Access Copies
  Subseries B: Originals
  Subseries C: Miscellaneous
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    Video materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - "New Year's"; "Video Theme Party", July 22, 1990; ID: 225.0001 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0001)
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Original format: VHS
    - "Gay Tards + Mini Red Satan, Surf Reality (1st NY perf.)", November 22, 2000; ID: 225.0002 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0002)
    - "Carmen Mofongo, Fiesta de Amor", February 11, 2005; ID: 225.0003 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0003)
    - "Feb 29, 2004; Matchgame '04", February 29, 2004; ID: 225.0004 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0004)
    - "To Hug U + Squeeze You (Kreider); Black Lagoon, It's Alive (Marv); His Holy Prepose (Gang); Industrial Synth (S Price); SSsion, Anorexia... (Cody); Sex Machine, Death Becomes Her 9 Times (Biddle)", undated; ID: 225.0016 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0016)
    - "Jacinto" (related to CVR?), undated; ID: 225/0019 (Box 10, Media ID: 225/0019)
    - "718-768-9079; AB25 OLOM, copy B1" [Subseries C?], January 16, 2000; ID: 225.0023 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0023)
    - "Stuff + AntiSlam Part 1", June 30, 2004; ID: 225.0036 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0036)
    - "Air Force Shoot", undated; ID: 225.0039 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0039)
      Original format: MiniDV
    - "Air Force Shoot", undated; ID: 225.0040 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0040)
    - "Ana Montana; CGC", March 2001; April 22, 2001; ID: 225.0041 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0041)
      Original format: Video 8
    - "AntiSlam (Summer '00?, 'Secretary Day-Evening', 'Baby Al'), 2000; ID: 225.0042 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0042)
      Original format: Hi8; Duration: 02:04:17
    - "Allesandro's Robosapien tryout, Fringe '99", 1999; ID: 225.0043 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0043)
    - "AntiSlam", January 2, 2004; ID: 225.0044 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0044)
    - "AntiSlam", Octiber 24, 2001; ID: 225.0045 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0045)
      Original format: VHS; Duration: 04:23:00
    - "AntiSlam (no audio)", March 24, 2004; ID: 225.0046 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0046)
    - "AntiSlam", January 4, 2004; ID: 225.0047 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0047)
      Original format: VHS; Duration: 06:15:56; Transfer Technician Note: "No audio on tape"
    - "AntiSlam", May 26, 2004; ID: 225.0048 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0048)
    - "AntiSlam", May 5, 2004; ID: 225.0049 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0049)
    - "AntiSlam", June 16, 2004; ID: 225.0050 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0050)
    - "AntiSlam", June 9,2004; ID: 225.0005 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0005)
    - "AntiSlam", June 22, 2004; ID: 225.0052 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0052)
    - "Chronis stuff, Tompkins Park", undated; ID: 225.0053 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0053)
    - "EP!; Convention; Music Builders; 3/26/1999", March 26, 1999; ID: 225.0054 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0054)
    - "Pixelface; Tesla party, 1999; 7/10/2004; ID: 225.0055 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0055)
    - "Neal Medlyn; Mr. LES (no audio)", January 2004; ID: 225.0056 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0056)
    - "CVR", undated; ID: 225.0057 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0057)
    - "Disco Sucks (2 min.); Faceboy 500 (no audio)", February 1, 2004; ID: 225.0058 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0058)
    - "Don't Ask Don't Tell trailer", undated; ID: 225.0059 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0059)
      Currently available until duplication occurs.
    - "Don't Ask Don't Tell trailer", undated; ID: 225.0060 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0060)
    - "Drama Desk Nomination", April 25, 2000; ID: 225.0061 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0061)
    - "Face[boy]", June 6, 2004; ID: 225.0062 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0062)
    - "Faceboy", May 16, 2004; ID: 225.0063 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0063)
    - "Faceboy", July 4, 2004; ID: 225.0064 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0064)
    - "Faceboy", May 23, 2004; ID: 225.0065 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0065)
    - "Monster 2001, #2", ID: 225.0066 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0066)
    - "LG", undated; ID: 225.0067 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0067)
    - "1) ???; 2)Magical Madness", July 27, 2001; ID: 225.0068 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0068)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 2: Viva La Revolucion (both nights)", 1997; ID: 225.0069 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0069)
      Original format: Hi8
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 2: Viva la Revolucion (2 nights; video by Steve Zacks)", 1997; ID: 225.0070 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0070)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 3: Factfinding tour (tight)" (side of cassette reads: "War is Cold #5"), January 10, 1998; ID: 225.0071 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0071)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 3: Factfinding tour; + Flint", January 9, 1998; ID: 225.0072 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0072)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 4: Operation Magna, (both nights)", January 30-31, 1998; ID: 225.0073 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0073)
    - "Manifestations 5", 1998; ID: 225.0074 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0074)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 5", 1998; ID: 225.0075 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0075)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 5: The Trans-Siberian Express", 1998; ID: 225.0076 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0076)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 6: Nutcracker", 1998; ID: 225.0077 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0077)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 8: Subterranean Homesick Blues", 5/31/1998; ID: 225.0078 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0078)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 8: Subterranean Homesick Blues", May 30, 1998; ID: 225.0079 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0079)
    - "Manifestations: War is Cold, Episode 9", August 29-30, 1998; ID: 225.0080 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0080)
    - "Match Game", April 2004; ID: 225.0081 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0081)
    - "Mermaid Parade, Monster Parade", 2001; ID: 225.0082 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0082)
    - "Mikon shots; Face (no audio)", February 29, 2004; ID: 225.0083 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0083)
      Currently unavailble until duplication occurs.
    - "9/4/04", September 4, 2004; ID: 225.0084 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0084)
    - "The Primary Principle, by Miroslaw Rajkowski (shot by Scott Kravet; Light & Sound by Steve Zacks)", July 11, 1998; ID: 225.0085 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0085)
    - "Rev Jen", undated; ID: 225.0086 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0086)
    - "Rev Jen's Halcyon Show; Autoevent #7", 1998; ID: 225.0087 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0087)
    - "shoots for 360 (degrees)", undated; ID: 225.0088 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0088)
    - "Tapp; Face", April 25, 2004; ID: 225.0089 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0089)
    - "Tesla Coil video, by Nick Zedd", undated; ID: 225.0090 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0090)
    - "Tesla moments; Faces", June 1, 2004; May 31, 2004; ID: 225.0091 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0091)
    - "Two Wishes Kissing, + Kelly dancing...", undated; ID: 225.0092 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0092)
    - "Two Wishes Kissing; War is Cold ep. 2 (last sc.); Steve (monologue)", undated; ID: 225.0093 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0093)
      Currently unavialable until duplication occurs.
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0094 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0094)
      Original format: VHS-C
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0095 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0095)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0096 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0096)
    - "Walker", September 30, 2000; ID: 225.0097 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0097)
    - "Mr. LES Farewell Address", undated; ID: 225.0152 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0152)
    - "Mr. LES show [crossed out]; movies" [Subseries C?], undated; ID: 225.0153 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0153)
    - "Scott Kravet, Museum of Experience, Sex Workers (21 Min.)", undated; ID: 225.0154 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0154)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    - "Queen of Outer Space", 1986; ID: 225.0005 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0005)
    - "Invasion of the Blood Farmers", 1986; ID: 225.0006 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0006)
    - "Mercury Rising", 1987; ID: 225.0007 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0007)
    - "Rollerball", 1975; ID: 225.0008 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0008)
    - "Leap of Faith", 1992; ID: 225.0009 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0009)
    - "Planet of the Apes", 1998; ID: 225.0010 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0010)
      Original Format: VHS
    - "Greatest Heroes of the Bible: The Ten Commandments/Abraham's Sacrifice", 1979; ID: 225.0011 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0011)
    - "The Running Man", 1987; ID: 225.0012 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0012)
    - "Lidsville, Vol. 1", undated; ID: 225.0013 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0013)
    - "Millenium Fever" (Subseries B?), undated; ID: 225.0014 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0014)
    - "WAHL Home Haircutting How-To Video", undated; ID: 225.0015 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0015)
    - "Bubblegum Crisis #5", undated; ID: 225.0017 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0017)
    - "Everting The Sphere" (Subseries B?), undated; ID: 225.0018 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0018)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0020 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0020)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0021 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0021)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0022 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0022)
    - "Bubblegum Crisis I,II,III,IV", undated; ID: 225.0024 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0024)
    - "(e)" (Subseries B?), undated; ID: 225.0025 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0025)
    - "Raw Justice", undated; ID: 225.0026 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0026)
    - "Stretch Marks vid" (Subseries B?), undated; ID: 225.0027 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0027)
    - "Blazing Saddles", undated; ID: 225.0028 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0028)
    - "Belle de Jour", undated; ID: 225.0029 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0029)
    - "Fists of Fury", undated; ID: 225.0030 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0030)
    - "Odyssey Animation, R.O. Ernst", August 1997; ID: 225.0031 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0031)
    - "J. Bond 147", undated; ID: 225.0032 (Box 10, Media ID: 225.0032)
    - "BJ, Scott Hess at HERE", undated; ID: 225.0033 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0033)
      Format: VHS
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0034 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0034)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 225.0035 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0035)
    - "The First Day of the Beginning of the End of the World, Jenny Stark", 1999; ID: 225.0037 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0037)
    - "A Fool and His Money", undated; ID: 225.0038 (Box 11, Media ID: 225.0038)
    - "a52, MVBMS, JP Morgan..." (container reads: "To Record"), undated; ID: 225.0098 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0098)
    - "Aguirre Der Zorn Gottes (The Wrath of God, with Klaus Kinski)", undated; ID: 225.0099 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0099)
    - "Al Fresco; (c) R. Shirley, Q. Williams", 1998; ID: 225.0100 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0100)
    - "60 Minutes of all Cornelius vids & Live Destruction; Directed by Corneius, Harvard Design, Help! Films", 2000; ID: 225.0101 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0101)
    - "Anarchy USA; The Commies are Coming; Red Menace; The Code of Conduct", 1965; 1953; undated; undated; ID: 225.0102 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0102)
    - "Architecture of Doom (about Nazi culture)", undated; ID: 225.0103 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0103)
    - "Attack of the 50ft. Woman", 1958; ID: 225.0104 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0104)
    - "Babe", 1995; ID: 225.0105 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0105)
    - "Battle of Algiers", 1993; ID: 225.0106 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0106)
    - "Big Trouble in Little China; Twins; Moon Over Parador", undated; ID: 225.0107 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0107)
    - "Black Magic M66 (48 min); Appleseed (70 min, Japanese cyberpunk animation)", undated; ID: 225.0108 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0108)
    - "Bondage, Vol. 1", undated; ID: 225.0109 (Box 12, Media ID: 225.0109)
    - "The Bride of Frankenstein", 1991; ID: 225.0110 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0110)
    - "Broadway...A History of the Musical: Vol II, Broadway Comes of Age", undated; ID: 225.0111 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0111)
    - "Brooklyn Burlesque Blitz; 1/12, Hour 3, Hosted by Naughtia Nice & Bastard Keith", undated; ID: 225.0112 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0112)
      Original format: DVD
    - "Cereal Commercials Vol. 1 & 2", undated; ID: 225.0113 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0113)
    - "Cheesedick, a tape by Matthew L. Weiss (Langdon-Boom Productions)", 2001; ID: 225.0114 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0114)
    - "16mm Classroom Films (Nostalgia Video)", undated; ID: 225.0115 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0115)
    - "Creepy Clips from Classic Horror Films!", 1995; ID: 225.0116 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0116)
    - "The Prisoner (Disc 2)" (container reads: "Demon Womb Check Disk"), July 21, 1999; ID: 225.0117 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0117)
    - "Diary of a Chambermaid (revised)", May 10. 2001; ID: 225.0118 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0118)
    - "Diderot and the Last Luminare (Erika Suderburg)", 1992; ID: 225.0119 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0119)
    - "Los Diez Mandamientos (The Ten Commandments)", 1980; ID: 225.0120 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0120)
    - "Comedy Central: 10PM -Dr Katz, ep. 601; 10:30PM -Mark Curry", June 15; ID: 225.0121 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0121)
    - "Fishing with John", March 17, 1999; ID: 225.0122 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0122)
    - "Flash Gordon (Vol. 1)", 1998; ID: 225.0123 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0123)
    - "Flash Gordon (Vol. 2)", 1998; ID: 225.0124 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0124)
    - "Flying in Airplane (Florida to NY), Steve Zacks" [Subseries B?], undated; ID: 225.0125 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0125)
    - "Frankie & Johnny", 1992; ID: 225.0126 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0126)
    - "Augustin Gimel - 1305, Radar, DIN 16538/39, Il n'y a rien de plus inutile qu'un organe, 90", undated; ID: 225.0127 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0127)
      Original format: VHS [PAL]
    - "Godzilla 2000", 1999; ID: 225.0128 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0128)
    - "Good News New York", undated; ID: 225.0129 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0129)
    - "TCM's Brownlow & Gill Comedy Masters Series - Harold Lloyd: The Third Genius", April 18, 1997; ID: 225.0130 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0130)
    - "Hitler's homemovies; Three Songs about Lenin ('39)", undated; ID: 225.0131 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0131)
    - "Hitler [illegible annotations] Quex", undated; ID: 225.0132 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0132)
    - "Hornet Magic (The Boeing Company)", 2000; ID: 225.0133 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0133)
    - "How To Get Ahead In Advertising, 6/7/01", June 7, 2001; ID: 225.0134 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0134)
    - "In Our Garden", undated; ID: 225.0135 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0135)
    - "Invasion of the Bee Girls", undated; ID: 225.0136 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0136)
    - "Invasion of the Saucer Men", 1993; ID: 225.0137 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0137)
    - "Ivan the Terrible, pt. 2", February 20, 2001; ID: 225.0138 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0138)
    - "Jericho Fever", 1993; ID: 225.0139 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0139)
    - "The Jungle Book", undated; ID: 225.0140 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0140)
    - "Justin Charisma", undated; ID: 225.0141 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0141)
    - "Lamb, Fear of Fours video reel", 1999; ID: 225.0142 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0142)
    - "Life in Bud, Nick Lindsay", undated; ID: 225.0143 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0143)
    - "Life on Earth", October 10, 2000; ID: 225.0144 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0144)
    - "Fourth Annual Media That Matters Film Festival", 2004; ID: 225.0145 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0145)
    - "The Troika Organization, 'Meet Me In St. Louis', television spot & selected songs", undated; ID: 225.0146 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0146)
    - "The Miracle of the One Visit Denture", undated; ID: 225.0147 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0147)
    - "Miracle on 34th Street", 1993; ID: 225.0148 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0148)
    - "Monster From Green Hell", 1990; ID: 225.0149 (Box 13, Media ID: 225.0149)
    - "Monster From A Prehistoric Planet", 1989; ID: 225.0150 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0150)
    - "MPFC German Episode 2", September 5, 2000; ID: 225.0151 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0151)
    - "9 to 5", 1995; ID: 225.0155 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0155)
    - "None of the Above (trailer), Insular Pictures, Frank Barrera", undated; ID: 225.0156 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0156)
    - Misc. taped programs on Nazism, undated; ID: 225.0157 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0157)
    - "Oui We, by Anthony Howard", undated; ID: 225.0158 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0158)
    - "Integrated Orbital Implants, Inc. Patient Education Video", undated; ID: 225.0159 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0159)
    - "USA Network: People's Court episodes 2182/2183", undated; ID: 225.0160 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0160)
    - "Piano Man and Medea excerpts, Dor Green", undated; ID: 225.0161 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0161)
    - "Pierrot le Fou", September 25, 1998; ID: 225.0162 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0162)
    - "Porky's II: The Next Day", 1983; ID: 225.0163 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0163)
    - "Prehistoric Women", 1985; ID: 2253.0164 (Box 14, Media ID: 2253.0164)
    - "The Prisoner Vol. 7", March 5, 2001; ID: 225.0165 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0165)
    - "Reveille, dir. Bruce Bennett (C:U storefront cameo)", 2001; ID: 225.0166 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0166)
    - "Rock 'n' Roll Frankenstein music video", undated; ID: 225.0167 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0167)
    - "Rock n Roll Frankenstein trailer", undated; ID: 225.0168 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0168)
    - "Rock 'N' Roll Frankenstein trailer", undated; ID: 225.0169 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0169)
    - "Safari, a film by Paul Sullivan", undated; ID: 225.0170 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0170)
    - "Salo check disc", undated; ID: 225.0171 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0171)
    - "Saya for Kristina Daniels", undated; ID: 225.0172 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0172)
    - "Dan Cronin as Sergi, video by Paul Sullivan", undated; ID: 225.0173 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0173)
    - "Shrimpdiabloinmypants Film Festival", July 10, 1999; ID: 225.0174 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0174)
    - "Erika Suderburg, Somatography", 2000; ID: 225.0175 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0175)
    - "South Dakota Trilogy In Three Minutes", undated; ID: 225.0176 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0176)
    - "The Adventures of Spunky and Tadpole", 1985; ID: 225.0177 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0177)
    - "Sugar Hill", undated; ID: 225.0178 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0178)
    - "Them!", undated; ID: 225.0179 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0179)
    - "Thunderbirds Vol 3", January 8, 2001; ID: 225.0180 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0180)
    - "To Have and Have Not", 1945; ID: 225.0181 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0181)
    - "Topaz", undated; ID: 225.0182 (Box 14, Media ID: 225.0182)